https://www.nlplifetraining.com/termsconditions

Terms and Conditions
Home
Product Purchase Terms & Conditions
Customer Support and Service
If you require any assistance please email us at info@thebestyou.co
Stock Availability
We try to keep everything in stock, however this isn't always possible. If an item is out of stock, we will email you within 3 working days of placing your order.
Delivery Costs
The delivery cost will be shown when you reach the checkout.  Please select the delivery option suitable for your location (UK, Europe, Rest of World).  We normally use Royal Mail Recorded Delivery, so a signature maybe required on delivery.  To avoid delay, please give a delivery address where this will be possible.
Online Viewing
The purchase of a Online Viewing entitles the client to view this online video for a maximum of 10 viewings within a 3 month period. Partial viewing will count as a full viewing. It is the client's responsibility to ensure their download Internet connection speed is sufficient to stream the video. We recommend a connection of at least 2MB/s to optimise the viewing experience. The viewing is strictly restricted to a maximum of three IP addresses. Please ensure your system meets the minimum requirements:
Minimum Desktop / Laptop requirements to watch Online Viewings
Microsoft Windows
Mac OS
Processor
Intel Pentium 4 2.33GHz,
Athlon 64 2800+
(or equivalent)
Intel Core™ Duo 1.66GHz
Memory
128MB RAM
256MB RAM
Graphics Memory
128MB
128MB
Minimum Operating System and browser requirements to watch Online Viewings on a PC
Windows Platform
Windows Browsers
Windows 7, Microsoft® Windows Vista®, or Microsoft Windows XP
Internet Explorer 7, Firefox 6, Chrome 13
Minimum Operating System and browser requirements to watch Online Viewings on a MAC
MAC Platform
MAC Browsers
Mac OS X v10.5 (Intel)
Safari 5.0, Firefox 6, Chrome 13
Physical Product Returns
We hope you that will be delighted with your purchase fromThe Best You or Associated companies. Should a product not arrive in satisfactory condition, the items should be returned within 7 days.
If you would like a refund, the items need to be in a perfect saleable condition in their undamaged, original packaging. We cannot refund or exchange anything that has been personalised. Return postage, packing insurance and direct costs cannot be refunded. Please keep proof of postage to facilitate claims should goods be lost in transit. We endeavour to handle all returns or complaints as soon as possible.
Cancellation of an Order
You can cancel your order at any time. If the goods have been dispatched already then you have 7 days to return your order to receive a refund. We cannot however refund any postage costs, either to send your order out or to receive it back.
Seminar & Courses Terms & Conditions
How to book
Booking can be made by telephone or online via the website.
Payment
To secure your booking 50% of the course fees must be paid in advance. Full payment must be made 6 weeks in advance of the course start date. VAT is chargeable at the prevailing rate.
Booking confirmation
You will be sent a booking confirmation by email on receipt of your payment which will contain details of the location, start times and other relevant details. If you have not received this within 48 hours of making your booking, please contact our office on +44 208 089 6972
Cancellations
If a participant fails to attend the course all fees are forfeited. Early booking cancellations are subject to the following terms:
Charging Period
Charge / Refunds
14 Days or less after booking date
Full Refund
More than 14 Days after booking date
No Refund
Within 30 days of the seminar start date
No Refund
Cancellation by The Best You
The company reserves the right to change dates and venues.  The Best You reserves the right to alter the course content, location or cancel any course at any time without liability.
Overseas visitors
Please ensure you have the authority to travel prior to booking the event. We are unable to liaise with the Visa authorities on your behalf. Our assistance to any third party is limited to confirmation of booking of the respective event.
Any booking that you make is subject to our standard terms and conditions, we recommend that you obtain your Visa as required prior to booking.
Course confirmation
We aim to confirm your place on the course within 24 hours of receiving your completed form and deposit. If you do not hear from us within a working week please contact our office on: +44 208 089 6972
Course disclamier
All delegates will be required to complete a disclaimer prior to attending a workshop, acceptance is at our sole discretion and we reserve the right to refuse admission to anyone without prejudice for any reason whatsoever.
The workshop/seminar/event may contain adult language that some individuals may find offensive. There is no audio or video recording/taping allowed.  All performances are protected under U.K. and international copyright law.  NLP Life and The Best You reserves the rights to use any recordings for marketing and website purposes only.
By attending a seminar the delegate/assistant consents to photography, audio recording, video recording its/their release, publication, exhibition, or reproduction to be used for news, web casts, promotional purposes, telecasts, advertising and inclusion on web sites. You release The Best You, its officers, employees, and any persons involved from any liability connected with the taking, recording, digitizing, or publication of interviews, photographs, computer images, video and/or or sound recordings.
By entering the event premises, you waive all rights you may have to any claims for payment or royalties in connection with any exhibition, streaming, webcasting, televising, or other publication of these materials, regardless of the purpose or sponsoring of such exhibiting, broadcasting, webcasting, or other publication.
Licensed NLP Master Practitioner bookings
Please note that in order to apply to the NLP Master Practitioner training you will need to have previously be trained by a reputable and established NLP Training company or organisation. The minimum days training are seven days and online training is not accepted.
Once you have booked and applied to the NLP Master Practitioner you will need to provide your NLP Practitioner certificate within 48 hours of booking, please email to info@nlplifetraining.com
If you do not provide a valid certificate the company reserves the right to transfer your booking to the Licensed NLP Practitioner course without any further notification.
General Terms & Conditions
Ownership & quality of information
Legal and beneficial title to all intellectual property rights existing in any documentation, data, know-how, methods and concepts, used or developed by us in providing the services, shall, as between you and us, belong to and remain vested in us.
All conditions or warranties (whether expressed or implied by statute or common law or arising from conduct or a previous course of dealing or trade custom or usage or otherwise) as to the quality of the session materials we supply or their fitness for a particular purpose (even if that purpose is made known expressly or by implication to us) are expressly excluded.
Data
When you place and order, all personal data provided to us will be used in accordance with data protection laws and our privacy policy.
Our promise
We will use all reasonable care and skill in providing the services you order under this agreement, but we do not guarantee any results of the services. Any decision you make having received any of our services are your own and you remain wholly responsible for any decisions and actions you take.
General issues
This agreement is the entire agreement between us and it supersedes any previous agreement between us relating to any services we provide, unless otherwise agreed in writing by us both. We both agree that by entering into this agreement, neither of us has relied on, and is not able to have any remedy, for any statement, promise, representation or understanding (whether it is made negligently or innocently) or any person other than what is expressly promised in this agreement. The only remedy available for breach of the promises in this agreement is for breach of contract. Nothing in this paragraph attempts to limit or exclude any liability for fraud.
No failure or delay in enforcing any of our rights under this agreement will prejudice or restrict those rights. If we waive our rights to require you to comply with this agreement it will not operate as a waiver or any further exercise of the right and a waiver of any breach will not operate as a waiver of any subsequent breach.
We both agree that each provision of this agreement is severable and distinct from any other. If any part of this agreement is found to be illegal, invalid or unenforceable in whole or in part, we both agree that the legality, validity and enforceability of the remainder of the agreement is not affected.
No terms of this agreement are intended for the benefit of any third party, except where expressly stated in this agreement, and we both agree that it is not intended that and the term of this agreement should be enforceable by a third party under the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act 1999. If you choose to make an order, these terms and conditions only apply to that order and not to any future orders.
Bookings are subject to the terms and conditions. Bookings cannot be confirmed until full payment has been received. All requests for cancellations and transfers must be confirmed in writing.
Privacy policy
The Best You takes your privacy seriously. In general, we use the personal information that we collect from you to identify personal preferences and match your needs with relevant products, and process any orders that you may make through our website.
Note: This policy only applies to websites hosted at and comprising part of the www.thebestyou.co service and not to the companies, individuals, organisations or other websites to which there are links.
Consent
Your use of this website signifies your consent to us collecting and using personal information about you as specified below in accordance with this Policy. Should we choose to change our Policy for any reason, the changes will be posted here, so that you are always kept informed of how we collect and use your personal information, and when we may disclose it.
If you are a thebestyou.co member this policy will be applied subject to any particular limitations or choices you made as part of the membership application procedure.
How do we collect information about you and how is it used?
You may provide personal information when communicating with us.
You may order a product or a service and give your name, email address, delivery address, credit or debit card number and expiry date so that the order can be processed and your products (or services where appropriate) delivered to you. Sometimes you may be asked for your telephone number.
If you enter a competition or promotion we will ask for your name, address and email address.
We will collect information about your tastes and preferences both when you tell us what these are and by analysis of customer traffic, including by using cookies
It may be that some of the personal information you give us (for instance about your lifestyle or health) is sensitive personal data within the meaning of the Data Protection Act 1998. Any such information ("sensitive information") will only be dealt with as described below.
It may be that you provide details of credit or debit cards or bank accounts in order to make payments to us. Any such information ("confidential financial information") will be dealt with as described below.
We may use personal information collected about you to personalise your visits to our website and recommend goods or services to you. We also use the information to help us develop the design and layout of our website to ensure that our sites are as useful and enjoyable as possible.
We may use personal information collected about you to let you know about functionality changes to our website or changes to our terms and conditions of use.
Sometimes we or our affiliated companies* might use the personal information collected about you to let you know about new goods, services or offers that you might find interesting. If you do not wish to receive this information, please send an email to info@thebestyou.co
With the exception of sensitive information and confidential financial information, your personal information may also be sold, traded or licensed to third parties (including third parties who may be located outside the European Economic Area) in order to enable them to send you details that they think will interest you. By submitting your personal information to us you consent to this transfer. If you do not wish to receive this information, please send an email to info@thebestyou.co
Traffic data
We may provide aggregate statistics about our sales, customers, traffic patterns and other site information to third parties, but these statistics will not include any information that could personally identify you.
Other disclosures
The Best You reserves the right to access and disclose individually identifiable information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate its systems properly or to protect itself or its users.
How do we protect your information?
Yhe Best You has strict security procedures covering the storage and disclosure of your information in order to prevent unauthorised access and to comply with the Data Protection Act 1998. This means that sometimes we may ask you for proof of identity before disclosing any personal information to you. The Best You does not store or capture any of your card or payment details on our website.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser. On revisiting this site our computer server will recognise the cookie, giving us information about your last visit. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance. If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use many features of our website.
Customer feedback and complaints
We welcome your questions and comments about privacy issues and the design of our website. Should you have such comments or have a complaint about how we are using your personal data, please send an email to info@thebestyou.co
Subscribe to our free 20 Step Guide to NLP
First Name *Last Name *Email *City *Country *Please select oneAfghanistanÅland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamas (the)BahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBolivia (Plurinational State of)Bonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean Territory (the)Brunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCabo VerdeCambodiaCameroonCanadaCayman Islands (the)Central African Republic (the)ChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) Islands (the)ColombiaComoros (the)Congo (the Democratic Republic of the)Congo (the)Cook Islands (the)Costa RicaCôte d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech Republic (the)DenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican Republic (the)EcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (the) [Malvinas]Faroe Islands (the)FijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern Territories (the)GabonGambia (the)GeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHoly See (the)HondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIran (Islamic Republic of)IraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJohnston IslandJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (the Democratic People's Republic of)Korea (the Republic of)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic Republic (the)LatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacaoMacedonia (the former Yugoslav Republic of)MadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall Islands (the)MartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia (Federated States of)Midway IslandsMoldova (the Republic of)MonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlands (the)New CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNiger (the)NigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana Islands (the)NorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippines (the)PitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRéunionRomaniaRussian Federation (the)RwandaSaint BarthélemySaint Helena, Ascension and Tristan da CunhaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Martin (French part)Saint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSouthern RhodesiaSpainSri LankaSudan (the)SurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwan (Province of China)TajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos Islands (the)TuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab Emirates (the)United KingdomUnited StatesUnited States Minor Outlying Islands (the)Upper VoltaUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic of)Viet NamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (U.S.)Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwePhone *I want to receive future discounts, offers & free training.I agree to the terms of serviceI agree to the privacy policy
Testimonial
I’d say my expectations have been exceeded, on many levels
Testimonial I’ve seen the benefits of the course
Testimonial I learned techniques how to have a better life
Testimonial William Fern - The Secret of Hypnosis
Testimonial Paul McKenna and Richard Bandler's The Secrets of Hypnosis - Testimonials II - London, May 2013
Who is Richard Bandler?
close
